<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Fookedonhonix]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Fookedonhonix]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/fookedonhonix/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 00:54:28 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/fookedonhonix/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[C is to B as]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>C is to B as</h1><p>As obsessed as max over 216 digits I follow that spiraling yellow brick road to a sunflower plant. Interestingly even the family tree of honeybees that pollinated these buzzed along the same path. Sound math painted the path of the great wave that makes reflections in water. The same reflections are seen in the pinecone and in the fruit sprouts of the pineapple. Over the horizon radar also directly follows the formula of this fruit but in listing only. Being lonely and obsessed, I recess to reading alone 289 times before the sacrament of the last supper. All summer these seeds formulaically flower revealing how aesthetics can be golden powered. Showered in numbers I count the drops, I get to 112358132134, but the rain never stops. Bartók’s sonata for two pianos and percussion patters to the rhythm. I listen closer, I’m driven. Seeing 1.618 is how it was written. To who do I owe for these divine proportions? Obsessed to the max, I’m dying, crying, infected, it’s viral. C is to b as, as I disappear into the infinite exterior of this spiral.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/fookedonhonix/c-is-to-b-as/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d748d591-3415-4e80-a4c3-df6152c45993</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 00:54:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radio Transmission Jamming]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Radio Transmission Jamming</h1><p>Geogaddi’s number station passes shortwave transmissions between left and right channels. You could probably play it in reverse at 3:34 and it would pan around the other way. Radio stations operate like this in dreams. Only this is not a dream, it sounds like something near the Boards of Canada. Spies were believed to receive messages from government agencies using this method. Conet Project, yes, the Conet Project revealed this from a Lincolnshire Poacher I hear. Only track four scans like this though, spinning speech synthesis around your head. Powerful in its function, but in this case, it’s all about the form of its sound. Even albums have something to say sometimes if you listen closely.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/fookedonhonix/7b1bd720-2d08-4c4c-a9ef-b7ec5db82f7d/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7b1bd720-2d08-4c4c-a9ef-b7ec5db82f7d</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 00:53:49 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>